sunnytoo.com 2018-12-16

# Privacy Policy - ST-THEMES

Last updated: 22 November 2017

To buy our products and services, you need to provide us your personal information. Your privacy is the most important thing to us. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that we collects, and the ways in which we use your personal information.

 **Data that you will provide here are processed by:**

Jonny Li

helloleemj@gmail.com

 **Personal information collection**  
For a better experience while using our site, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to your name, email address, and postal address. The information that we collect will be used to contact or identify you.

 **Using personal information:**

All data that you will provide will not be sold anywhere, and they will be used only for order purposes (invoices for order). So these informations can be used:

  * to collect and identify payments from you;
  * to send you digital products that you purchased;
  * to send you information about order status and creating account process;
  * to generate and send an invoice for the order;
  * to assist us in analyzing how our services are used.

 **Cookies Policy**  
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier.  
Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.  
Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

Remember that you can disable cookies in your web browser settings.

 **Contact Us**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](https://www.sunnytoo.com/contact).
